{
    "id": "ec116582de454feca5c0499ecc00fb44",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They swam ………………….. the river.",
            "description": "We usually prefer across to talk about movement in water.",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They live in a village just ………………………… the border.",
            "description": "Across and over can mean on or to the other side of a line, river, road etc.",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "over",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I work best ……………………….. the evening.",
            "description": "We use in with parts of the day.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "See you …………………….. Saturday evening.",
            "description": "Before days we use on.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can run 400 meters ………………………. about one minute.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "in",
                "within"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We usually go and see grandmother …………………………. Sunday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That car can seat ……………………….. seven people.",
            "description": "To talk about quantity we use up to.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "as far as",
                "upto"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I won’t be seeing him ………………………. Wednesday.",
            "description": "Not until can mean the same as not before.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "before",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The nearest restaurant is about half a mile ………………………….. the road.",
            "description": "Sometimes both up and down can mean along.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "None of the last six trains has been ………………………….. time.",
            "description": "On time means at the planned time.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He could have been saved if they had brought him to hospital ………………………….. time.",
            "description": "In time means before the last moment.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been here …………………………. three weeks now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}